### **Ben Prince**

Email: <a href="mailto:bprin87@gmail.com">bprin87@gmail.com</a>
Mobile: 07798907313

Portfolio: https://benprince.co.uk/

LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/ben-prince-aa9111254

GitHub: https://github.com/bprin87

#### **Personal Statement**

I am a mature third year student studying Web Design & Development at Edge Hill University. I have studied a wide range of modules including, but not limited to, Web Application Development, Server & Client-Side Scripting, Mobile Applications & Games Development, and User Experience Design.

# **Key Technical Skills**

HTML5: 8 projects developed
 CSS3: 8 projects developed
 JavaScript: 5 projects developed
 React: 4 projects developed
 PHP: 1 project developed

MySQL: 1 project developed
 Python: 1 project developed
 Java: 1 project developed

UX/UI

#### **Education**

### BSc (Hons) Web Design & Development

Edge Hill University, September 2021 – Present

### Modules studied include:

- Web Application Development
- Data Driven Design
- Server & Client-Side Scripting
- Mobile Applications Development

- User Experience Design
- Usability Testing & Data Analysis

# **Portfolio Projects:**

- Currently building a novel Generous Interface in the form of an interactive world map using React, which allows users to explore digital cultural heritage collections based on their place of origin.
- Using PHP with Laravel and MySQL, creates an online questionnaire system which allows users to create questionnaires and save submissions.

#### BA (Hons) Drama and Film & Television Studies

Manchester Metropolitan University, 2005 - 2009

A Level: History, Drama and Design Technology GCSE's: 8 GCSE's A-C including Math and English

St Mary's College, Crosby 1999-200

# **Employment History**

### **Supervisor & Bartender**

Woodward's Win Bar, October 2021 – present

- Providing customer service
- Handling complaints
- Daily cash and audit reconciliation

#### **Scheduling & Time Utilisation Analyst**

Assurant, July 2018 – November 2020

- Ensuring operational resource was scheduled to the highest standards through analysing detailed customer behaviour
- Working with senior management in regard to ensuring cost effective resource usage.
- · Reviewing schedule rotation balances to provide shift coverage across multiple departments
- Regularly reviewing part-time staffing requirements in line with the business's needs
- Monitoring operational performance, identifying trends and areas for investigation and analysis
- Analysing, producing, and maintaining MI for relevant stakeholders

#### **Intraday Manager**

Assurant November 2012 - July 2018

- Overseeing the resourcing of a busy call centre operation
- Looking after the bespoke service levels that contractually needed to be achieved on a weekly/monthly basis
- Ensuring department KPI's were adhered to whilst maintaining service levels

#### **Customer Service Advisor**

Assurant July 2009-November 2012

- Complaint management including call escalations
- Understanding business regulations such as TCF, Vulnerable Customer and GDPR
- Processing refunds

### **Personal Interests**

I lead a relatively healthy lifestyle and enjoy lifting weights and going out running and I spend a lot of my spare time learning Spanish and developing projects.

References available on request